strucr.com 2017-10-19

# Audisto Privacy Policy

### 1\. General Information 

**1.1.** This Privacy Policy has been designed to inform you and notify you of the kinds, the scope and the purpose, as well as your rights concerning your data collected and processed by Audisto GmbH, Hans-Thoma-Str. 4, 76593 Gernsbach, Germany. 

**1.2.** By visiting our websites and using our services you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

### 2\. Definitions

**2.1.** Personally Identifiable Data - This kind of data can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person or can be used with other sources to uniquely identify a single individual (e.g. names, e-mail-addresses). 

**2.2.** Pseudonymous Data - The pseudonymous data identifies a holder, that is, one or more human beings who possess but do not disclose their true names (e.g. "user5623"). 

**2.3.** Cookies - A cookie is a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in a user's web browser while a user is browsing a website. When the user browses the same website in the future, the data stored in the cookie can be retrieved by the website to notify the website of the user's previous activity. We use Cookies in order to improve the usability of our services as well as for analyzing and personalizing purposes. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually refuse cookies or selectively accept certain cookies by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn off cookies, there may some features of our site that will not be available to you and some web pages may not display properly. 

**2.4.** IP Address - An Internet Protocol address (IP address) is a numerical label assigned to each device (e.g., computer, printer) participating in the Internet. We store the IP address only, if it is necessary to provide a service or if may be legally necessary. 

### 3\. Collection, Processing and Use of Personally Identifiable Data

**3.1.** We will collect, process and use personally identifiable data beyond the scope already permitted by law and without your required further consent only to the extent necessary for the conclusion and execution of a contractual relationship, performing requests or for billing purposes. 

**3.2.** Usage data, such as information regarding start and end dates and the scope of the use of certain services and/or communication data will only be collected, processed and used if this is necessary to make available and invoice such services. 

**3.3.** To protect your personally identifiable data collected and processed by us from unauthorized access and abuse, we have put a number of technical and organizational security measures in place. These security measures are monitored on a regular basis and updated according to technical progress as necessary. 

**3.4.** As provided for by applicable provisions we are entitled to disclose and submit data for criminal prosecution and risk prevention purposes. 

**3.5.** During every visit of our websites information about IP address, referring URL, date/time, browser version and operating system is stored in the web server log files due to technical and security reasons. 

### 4\. Sending Information by Newsletter and Email

**4.1.** Newsletters and emails that are not service-related and contain advertisement will only be send to you, if you have given us your prior consent. 

**4.2.** The content of the newsletter or email follows from its respective description. If no description is available, the content sent comprises information about us and our services, as well as information on our events or third party information and events. 

**4.3.** If you no longer want to receive our newsletter you can opt to stop receiving it at any time.

**4.4.** We save users‘ IP addresses as part of the log-on process. We are legally bound to record the log-on process so as to be able to verify that logging on is done in accordance with regulations. 

### 5\. Incorporation of third party services and content

**5.1.** Third party content, such as videos from YouTube, map material from Google Maps, RSS feeds and graphics from other websites, for example, can be incorporated on the website. 

**5.2.** This always presupposes that the provider of this content (hereafter referred to as the “third party provider”) always uses the user’s IP address. This is because without the IP address, they cannot send the content to the respective user’s browser. The IP address is thus required for displaying this content. 

**5.3.** We endeavour only to use content of which the respective provider uses the IP address only for distributing the content. However, we have no influence on whether the third party provider saves the IP address for other purposes, such as statistical purposes, for example. If we are aware of this, we will clarify this in the following paragraphs. 

### 6\. Google Analytics

**6.1.** This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . 

**6.2.** In case IP-anonymisation is activated on this website, your IP address will be truncated within the area of Member States of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases the whole IP address will be first transferred to a Google server in the USA and truncated there. The IP-anonymisation is active on this website. 

**6.3.** Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing them other services relating to website activity and internet usage. 

**6.4.** The IP-address, that your Browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics, will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You can also opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your current web browser: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>. 

**6.5.** As an alternative to the browser add-on or within browsers on mobile devices, you can click this link in order to opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics within this website in the future. An opt-out cookie will be stored on your device, which means that you'll have to click this link again, if you delete your cookies. 

### 7\. Google Double Click

**7.1.** This website uses Google's Double Click Technology, a remarketing service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google's Double Click Technology uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer for Online Behavioral Advertising (OBA). The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . 

**7.2.** Online Behavioral Advertising uses information collected across multiple websites that you visit to predict your preferences or infer interests and to show you ads that are more likely to be of interest to you. Please visit for detailed information [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**7.3.** You can opt out of DoubleClick's use of cookies by visiting the DoubleClick opt-out page <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb#display_optout> or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

### 8\. Use of Facebook Social Plugins

**8.1.** Our website uses social plugins (“plugins”) provided by the social network facebook.com, operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). The plugins are identifiable by a Facebook logo (white letter f on blue background or a thumb up icon) or the notice “Facebook Social Plugin”. For a full list of all social Plugins please see <https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>. 

**8.2.** When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to Facebook servers. Facebook directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling Facebook to receive information about your having accessed the respective page of our website. Thus we have no influence on the data gathered by the plugin and inform you according to our state of knowledge: 

**8.3.** The embedded plugins provide Facebook with the information that you have accessed the corresponding page of our website. If you are logged into Facebook, your visit can be assigned to your Facebook account. If you interact with the plugins, for example by clicking “Like”, or entering a comment, the corresponding information is transmitted from your browser directly to Facebook and stored by it. Even if you are not logged into Facebook, there is possibility that the plugins transmits your IP-address to Facebook. 

**8.4.** For the information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Facebook, as well as your rights in this respect and settings options for protecting your privacy please visit Facebook’s privacy policy: <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>. 

**8.5.** If you are a Facebook member and do not want Facebook to connect the data concerning your visit to our website with your member data already stored by Facebook, please log off from Facebook before entering our website. Further you can block Facebook social Plugins by using add-ons for your browser, like the “Facebook Blocker”. 

### 9\. Use of Google's +1 Button

**9.1.** This website uses the “+1″-Button provided by the social network Google+, operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 (“Google”). The button is identifiable by a Google "g" logo with a "+1". When a user visits a page of this website that contains a +1 Button, his browser establishes a direct connection to Google servers. Google directly transfers the +1 Button's content to user's browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling Google to receive information about the user having accessed the respective page of this website. Thus the Service Provider have no influence on the data gathered by Google and informs users according to its state of knowledge: In accordance to Google the +1 Button doesn't collect any personally identifiable data on users unless they are members of the Google+ Network. 

**9.2.** For the information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Google, as well as user's rights in this respect and settings options for protecting user's privacy please visit Google's privacy policy: <http://www.google.de/intl/en/policies/privacy/>. 

### 10\. Use of Twitter Buttons

**10.1.** This website uses Twitter-Buttons (e.g. "Twitter this", "Twitter", "Follow @twitter") provided by the service Twitter, operated by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. When a user visits a page of this website that contains a Twitter-Button, his browser establishes a direct connection to Twitter servers. Twitter directly transfers the Twitter-Button's content to user's browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling Twitter to receive information about the user having accessed the respective page of this website. Thus the Service Provider have no influence on the data gathered by Twitter and informs users according to its state of knowledge: In accordance to Twitter, its buttons doesn't collect any personally identifiable data on users. 

**10.2.** For the information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Twitter, as well as user's rights in this respect and settings options for protecting user's privacy please visit Twitter's privacy policy: <http://twitter.com/privacy>. 

### 11\. Use of Visual Website Optimizer

**11.1.** We are using the Visual Website Optimizer (a service of Wingify Software Private Limited, 404, Gopal Heights, Netaji Subhash Place, Pitam Pura, Delhi 110034, India), in order to improve the usability of our website. Visual Website Optimizer allows us to test how changes of our website (i.e. size of input forms, graphics, font sizes) are perceived by our users (so called "A/B-Testing"). 

**11.2.** Only for these testing purposes Visual Website Optimizer sets cookies on user's Devices. Visual Website Optimizer does not store IP address or any other personally identifiable information. By the nature of its Service, Visual Website Optimizer will gather non-personally identifiable statistics about the usage of our website and store that information. Visual Website Optimizer will not share this website statistics without your consent. 

**11.3.** For further information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Visual Website Optimizer, as well as user's rights in this respect and settings options for protecting user's privacy please visit Visual Website Optimizer 's privacy policy: <http://visualwebsiteoptimizer.com/privacy-policy.php>. 

**11.4.** In case you (or your website visitors or users) want to opt out of tracking by Visual Website Optimizer anyway, please follow this link, clicking on which will exclude you from any kind of tracking by Visual Website Optimizer: <https://audisto.com/?vwo_opt_out=1>

### 12\. Mouseflow

**12.1.** We are using "Mouseflow" an analysing tool by Mouseflow ApS, Skindergade 15, 1159 Copenhagen K, Denmark, [http://mouseflow.com](http://mouseflow.com/). Mouseflow provides us with reports regarding visitor interactions on our website, that may include for example: aggregate reports of clicking or mouse movement activity, aggregate reports of scrolling activity and recreation of visitor browsing sessions with heatmaps or videos. Additionally Mouseflow collects technical data, like language, operating system, screen resolution or browser client. 

**12.2.** Mouseflow stores session information in cookies that are used to ensure accurate data is extracted from our systems. These cookies are temporary 1st party cookies (cookie will be deleted after users leave the website and cannot be shared across websites) and do not include any personal data. 

**12.3.** Mouseflow does not collect personally identifiable data or creates user profiles. IP-addresses will be anonymized and the collected information will not be transferred to third parties. All the information we collect via Mouseflow has the solely purpose of improving the usability of our services. Please refer to Mouseflow's privacy policy for further information: <http://mouseflow.com/privacy>. 

**12.4.** In case you want to opt out of tracking by Mouseflow anyway, please follow this link and click on „Disable Mouseflow“ which will exclude you from any kind of tracking by Mouseflow: <http://mouseflow.com/opt-out>. 

### 13\. Optimizely

**13.1.** We are using Optimizely ([https://www.optimizely.com](https://www.optimizely.com/), 631 Howard Street, Suite 100 San Francisco, CA 94105, USA), in order to improve the usability of our website. Optimizely allows us to test how changes of our website (i.e. size of input forms, graphics, font sizes) are perceived by our users (so called "A/B-Testing"). 

**13.2.** Only for these testing purposes Optimizely sets cookies on user's devices. Optimizely does not store IP address or any other personally identifiable information. By the nature of its Service, Optimizely will gather non-personally identifiable statistics about the usage of our website and store that information. Optimizely will not share this website statistics without your consent. 

**13.3.** For further information on the purpose and scope of data collection and procession by Optimizely, as well as user's rights in this respect and settings options for protecting user's privacy please visit Optimizely's privacy policy: <http://www.optimizely.com/privacy>. 

**13.4.** In case you want to opt out of tracking by Optimizely anyway, please follow this link, clicking on which will exclude you from any kind of tracking by Optimizely: <https://audisto.com/?optimizely_opt_out=true> (more information on the opt-out: <https://www.optimizely.com/opt_out>). 

### 14\. Contact and Notices

In compliance with legal requirements we will at any time provide you with information on your personally identifiable data stored by us, free of charge and without undue delay. Furthermore, you are free to revoke the approvals granted by confirming this Privacy Policy, at any time and with future effect. If you wish to do so, please feel free to contact us. 

### 15\. Necessary Amendments

We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy with view to the provision of new services, if and to the extent necessary. The same applies if the current Privacy Policy is found to contain any gaps. Upon such amendment, we will contact our Users by email sent to the email address provided to us.
